theladders.co.uk 2013-04-26

# TheLadders.co.uk privacy policy

**Privacy Policy**

We are committed to protecting and respecting your privacy.

This policy sets out the basis on which any personal data we collect from you, or that you provide to us, will be processed by us. Please read the following carefully.

For the purposes of the Data Protection Act 1998 (the "Act"), we, TheLadders.co.uk Limited (company number 06244717) are the data controller. We have our registered office at The Copper Room, Deva Centre, Trinity Way, Manchester M3 7BG.

This Privacy Policy explains the collection, use, and disclosure of personal data through our site. "Personal data" includes information such as your name, address, telephone number, or email address.

We may revise this Privacy Policy at any time. Any changes we make in the future will be posted on this page.

**Information We Collect**

We may collect and process the following personal data:

•                Information that you provide by filling in our basic registration forms, contacting us, subscribing to our services or posting material. We use this information to contact you about further services on our Sites.

•                Information relating to the jobs you've applied to, jobs you've viewed on the site, your CV submitted and similar information.

We will never rent or sell your personal data to third parties for marketing purposes and we will only share your contact information with a recruiter or hiring manager, in accordance with our terms of use, and the settings for your account.

Personal data may be shared with third parties responsible for purging our mailing lists. In such cases, personal data will only be shared if that third party agrees to comply with procedures and policies which are compliant with our procedures and policies regarding data protection and if that third party has put in place adequate measures which are compliant with the applicable law. Such third parties may be located outside the European Union. By submitting personal data to us, you agree to the transfer of personal data to those third parties.

We may use third parties to provide credit card processing services on our Sites. Sensitive information such as your income level and credit card information will be kept completely private and is secured with all reasonable industry standard protocols and technology.

The amount of information you choose to keep confidential is entirely up to you. You may upload or enter as much or as little information as you choose. All information posted will be visible to other users, recruiters (or their agents) and companies seeking employees in accordance with the settings of your account.

We use customer reviews for marketing and publicity purposes, which may contain personally identifiable information such as a customer's name. We obtain the customer's consent prior to posting their name along with their review.

**IP Addresses and Use of "Cookies"**

We may collect information about your computer, including where available your internet protocol ("IP") address, operating system and browser type, for system administration and to report aggregate information to our advertisers. An IP address is a number that is automatically assigned to your computer when you use the internet. We use IP addresses to help diagnose problems with our server, administer our site, analyse trends, track users' movement, gather broad demographic information for aggregate use in order for us to improve our site, and deliver customised, personalised content.

We use cookies to enhance your experience on our site. Cookies are pieces of information that are stored on the hard drive of your computer.

The following cookies are used on the Sites:

•                A cookie which stores information about your preferences; and

•                A cookie which saves your passwords and recognizes you when you return to our Site.

We also use a third party cookie (Google Analytics) to track user patterns, where visitors to the Site have come from and the pages they have visited. We do this in order to determine the usefulness of the information we supply to you. We do not correlate this information with data about individual users, nor do we share this information or sell it to a third party. We do not link the information we store in cookies to any personally identifiable information you submit while on our site.

You may refuse to accept cookies. However, if you do so, you may be unable to access certain parts of our Sites.

**Where We Store Your Personal Data**

The personal data that we collect from you may be transferred to, and stored at, a destination outside the European Economic Area ("EEA"). Data also be processed by staff who work for us or by one of our suppliers. By submitting your personal data to us, you agree to this transfer and processing. We will take all steps reasonably necessary to ensure that your data is treated securely and in accordance with this Privacy Policy.

We have implemented and follow industry standard measures to protect against unauthorised access to and unlawful interception or processing of personal data. We also protect account information by placing it on a secure portion of our site that is only accessible by a limited number of our qualified employees.

Where we have given you (or where you have chosen) a password which enables you to access certain parts of our Sites, you are responsible for keeping this password confidential.

Nevertheless, the transmission of information via the internet is not completely secure. Although we will do our best to protect your personal data, we cannot guarantee the security of your data transmitted to our Sites and any transmission is at your own risk.

**Uses Made of the Information**

We use the information held about you in the following ways:

•                To ensure that content from our site is presented in the most effective manner for you and for your computer;

•                To provide you with information, products or services that you request from us or which we feel may interest you, where you have consented to be contacted for such purposes;

•                To carry out our obligations arising from any contracts entered into between you and us;

•                To notify you about changes to our service;

•                To provide you with information, products or services that you request from us or which we feel may interest you.

You can subscribe or unsubscribe to our email services by changing your account settings.

We may share anonymous statistical information with other people. We only share your personal data in the limited situations set out in this policy, and we never sell or rent your personal data to third parties.

**Disclosure of personal data**

We may disclose your personal data to third parties:

•                If we seek to maintain, enhance, or add to the functionality of our site;

•                In the event that we sell or buy any business or assets, in which case we may disclose your personal data to the prospective seller or buyer of such business or assets;

•                If we becomes part of another organisation, that organisation will possess the personal data collected by us, and it will assume the rights and obligations regarding your personal data as described in this Privacy Policy;

•                If we are under a duty to disclose or share your personal data in order to comply with any legal obligation, or in order to enforce or apply our Terms of Use and other agreements; or to protect the rights, property, or safety of our customers, employees or others.

**Your Rights**

You have the right to ask us not to process your personal data for marketing purposes. If you change your mind, you may opt-out by changing your account settings.

**Access to Information**

The Act gives you the right to access information held about you. Your right of access can be exercised in accordance with the Act. Any access request is subject to a fee of £10 to meet our costs in providing you with details of the information we hold about you. **  
**
